This Cangyue,
when she first arrived,
wanted to find a chance to seduce His Majesty.
I didn't expect her to actually succeed.
I guess she will be a concubine soon.
Our small maid's room
can no longer accommodate a big shot like her.
That's right.
His Majesty is so temperamental.
In case she doesn't come back alive,
let's quickly pack her things and throw them out
to get rid of the bad luck.
Cangyue.
Oh, you're back.
Don't tell me you slept with him for a night
and got nothing in return.
What are you doing?
What are we doing?
Telling you to get out.
We don't have room for a vixen like you here.
Throw her stuff out.
I'd like to see you try.
Why wouldn't we?
Teach her a good lesson.
Mom!
Mom.
Apologize to me.
I'm sorry.
Louder.
It seems
it's time to teach you some rules.
Have you all learned?
Yes.
At ease.
Attention.
Parade rest.
Count off! 1 2 3 4 5 6.
My college military training wasn't in vain.
[Coughing]
Paying respects to Eunuch Sun.
How was it at His Majesty's palace last night?
Not bad.
Get ready.
You're on duty for His Majesty tonight.
I see you caught His Majesty's eye,
so I'm looking out for you.
Seize the opportunity.
And for wealth and glory,
you'll never have to worry again.
Thank you, Eunuch Sun.
Your Majesty.
Didn't I tell you to get out?
I am here to serve you for your bath and change of clothes.
Cang Yue.
Did Eunuch Sun send you?
Yes.
This time, a different one has arrived.
Take them off.
Why are you so slow?
I thought someone who wasn't afraid of me had come,
but I didn't expect you came to take my life.
My aunt's tricks are getting more and more clever.
You deserve to die.
Why?
How dare you ask such a thing?
I am the Holy Maiden of the Moon Shadow Clan.
We, the people of the Moon Shadow Clan,
are indifferent to fame and wealth, and aloof from the world.
I lived happily every day.
My parents treated me very well.
They were kind-hearted.
Later, I heard you ordered the slaughter of my entire clan
and the murder of my parents.
You really are the Holy Maiden of the Yueying Clan.
Yes.
What happened to the Yueying Clan?
Is anyone still alive?
They are all dead.
As far as the eye could see.
Corpses everywhere.
What are you laughing at?
Forget it.
Kill me if you want.
Don't you want revenge?
I will give you a chance.
Only one chance.
Why aren't you doing it?
That's not right.
Don't the characters I kill in this game
disappear automatically?
How could they?
Hello, player.
Key character death detected.
The plot point has been automatically reset.
This is reloading a save.
I killed the wrong person.
Don't you want revenge?
I will give you a chance.
Let me try again.
Only one chance.
Warning.
There are only two reset chances.
If the plot is interrupted again,
the experience will be terminated immediately.
Don't you want revenge?
I will give you a chance.
I'll only give you one chance.
Are you still not making your move?
You are not going to kill me?
I believe Your Majesty did not wipe out the Yueying Tribe.
I just want to know
who is the mastermind behind this.
Experiencer's task objective is 25% complete.
You don't need to know.
Since you are a daughter of the Yueying Tribe,
I will send someone to escort you out of the palace
to keep you safe for the rest of your life.
But I want to know the truth.
Your Majesty.
You know the truth.
I don't.
After all this,
the target of revenge isn't Si Xingxuan.
Then who is it?
Oh, Miss Cangyue.
Eunuch Sun.
Rubik's Cube.